{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"11.8.0","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":1470,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":10,"width":970,"height":535,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html","isVRProject":false},"contentStructure":[{"id":"SmartShape_32","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_32","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_33","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_33","title":"Press the F3 key to show the “NAVIGATOR” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_17","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["12609263"]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_15","title":"Press the F3 key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide14479","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_32","SmartShape_33","Text_Entry_Box_17","Hint_Shape_15"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":120},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide14479"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_7","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_7","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["IADEA"]},"constraints":{"length":5}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_16","title":"In the “Trans ID” field of the “NAVIGATOR” screen, enter IADEA to reach the “AUTORECEIVE BILL OF LADING” screen. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_1","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_1","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_4","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_4","title":"Click the white box and type IADEA. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_12","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7911","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_7","SmartShape_16","Success_Shape_1","Hint_Shape_4","Failure_Shape_12"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7911"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_8","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["000711904"]},"constraints":{"length":9}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_18","title":"Type in required zeros (000), then the Bill of Lading Number: 711904 in the “APPOINTMENT No” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_35","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_35","title":"Note that the Bill Of Lading Number must be 9 characters. If the number does not have 9 characters, 0’s must be added at the beginning. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_2","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_2","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_5","title":"Click the white box and type ‘000711904’. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_13","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7944","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_8","SmartShape_18","SmartShape_35","Success_Shape_2","Hint_Shape_5","Failure_Shape_13"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7944"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_10","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_21","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_21","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_19","title":"Press Tab to the “Arrv. Date/Time” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_8","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7977","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_10","SmartShape_21","SmartShape_19","Hint_Shape_8"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7977"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_11","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_24","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_24","title":" ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"SmartShape_26","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_26","title":"Press Tab to the “Arrival Door” field. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_9","title":"Press the Tab key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8037","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_11","SmartShape_24","SmartShape_26","Hint_Shape_9"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8037"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_12","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_12","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["001"]},"constraints":{"length":3}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_27","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_27","title":"Enter the door number (001) in the “Arrival Door” field. Then, press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_5","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_10","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_10","title":"Click the white box and type ‘001’ then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_16","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8097","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_12","SmartShape_27","Success_Shape_5","Hint_Shape_10","Failure_Shape_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8097"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_28","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_28","title":"A message response will appear, type Y for “Yes” and press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_13","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["Y"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_6","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_6","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_11","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_11","title":"Click the white box and type Y then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_17","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_17","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8130","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_28","Text_Entry_Box_13","Success_Shape_6","Hint_Shape_11","Failure_Shape_17"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8130"}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_18","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_18","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":[]},"constraints":{"length":0}}}},{"id":"SmartShape_36","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_36","title":"The Appointment Number (1528) is automatically generated in the “APPOINTMENT No” field.  Make a note of this number. Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_16","title":"Press the Enter key. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8163","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Entry_Box_18","SmartShape_36","Hint_Shape_16"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8163"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_30","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_30","title":"A warning message and Purchase Order(s) will appear, press Y  to select “Auto D/E Auto Ver” and then press Enter to accept. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_15","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_15","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["Y"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_8","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_8","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_13","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_13","title":"Click the white box and type Y then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_19","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_19","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8223","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_30","Text_Entry_Box_15","Success_Shape_8","Hint_Shape_13","Failure_Shape_19"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8223"}}},{"id":"SmartShape_31","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SmartShape_31","title":"A response message will appear, press Y for “Yes” and press Enter ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Entry_Box_16","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Entry_Box_16","roles":{"textEntry":{"question":"","correctAnswers":{"caseMatters":false,"answers":["Y"]},"constraints":{"length":1}}}},{"id":"Success_Shape_9","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Success_Shape_9","title":"Correct! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Hint_Shape_14","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Hint_Shape_14","title":"Click the white box and type Y then press Enter. ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Failure_Shape_20","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Failure_Shape_20","title":"Try again! ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide8256","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["SmartShape_31","Text_Entry_Box_16","Success_Shape_9","Hint_Shape_14","Failure_Shape_20"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":150},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide8256"}}},{"id":"Pool423","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":423,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"OpenPOIADEAtraining","class":"project","title":"OpenPOIADEAtraining","children":["Slide14479","Slide7911","Slide7944","Slide7977","Slide8037","Slide8097","Slide8130","Slide8163","Slide8223","Slide8256"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":379,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":[],"minScore":0,"maxScore":0,"passScore":0}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":true,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"launch_content","SCCriteria":"launch_content","exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide14479","title":"Slide 1"},{"id":"Slide7911","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide7944","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide7977","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide8037","title":"Slide 5"},{"id":"Slide8097","title":"Slide 6"},{"id":"Slide8130","title":"Slide 7"},{"id":"Slide8163","title":"Slide 8"},{"id":"Slide8223","title":"Slide 9"},{"id":"Slide8256","title":"Slide 10"}]}